SHORENA K. **ANZHILOV**

Software Engineer







I am a team-oriented, highly motivated, and passionate full-stack software developer. I use clean, maintainable code to create ethical, accessible software products. With cross-industry practice background and ten years of experience in business operations and management, I drive teams to achieve exceptional creative problem solutions. I am a dependable professional with dynamic communication skills, eager to contribute to company and team success.

CONTACT



(786) 247-7378



shorenaanzhilov@gmail.com



Miami Beach, FL

COMPUTER LANGUAGES

- ► HTML5
- Mongoose
- CSS3
- JSON
- Python
- EJS
- Django
- Typescript
- JavaScript(ES6)

DATABASE

- MongoDB
- VSCode
- Heroku
- PostgreSql
- ► (Git/Github)
- JSON API
- RESTful Routing

LIBRARIES & FRAMEWORKS

- React
- Node.js
- Express.js
- Bootstrap
- Node.js
- Django

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Dependable

Additional

Active Listener

Languages:

Problem Solver & Strategist Russian (Fluent) Georgian (Fluent) Spanish (Basic)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

Portfolios | Full-stack web application

Software Engineer 10/2022

Online portfolio directory, exposure tool for members to showcase experience and coding projects.

- Python, PostgreSQL, Django, CSS, HTML.
- · Utilized Django REST framework to build backend.
- Implemented Python and Django decorators for full CRUD functionality.
- Used HTML, CSS3 for UI on the frontend
- Utilized Git control during the production with frequent commits until deployment.

MyBooksy | Full-Stack MERN application

Software Engineer 09/2022

A book web app to find reviews on participating books or to buy your next read. Users can also publish their own book and add affiliate link for extra exposure.

- JavaScript, CSS, HTML, React, Express.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Mongoose, Postman.
- ► Full- Stack MERN application with full CRUD capabilities
- Collaborated in a team of 4 software engineers in a 1-week sprint an agile environment.
- Node.js, Express, Mongoose and MongoDB to build backend.
- React framework to build components and pages.
- Used React libraries and CSS3 for better UI on the frontend. Utilized Git control during the production with frequent commits until deployment..

Black Jack | Front-end web game

Software Engineer 08/2022

Online browser-based Blackjack card game

- JavaScript, CSS, HTML.
- Implemented JavaScript for game functionality with DOM manipulation to render elements.
- Utilized Git control during the production with frequent commits until deployment.

MORE SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

KIBI | Full-Stack MEN application

Software Engineer 08/2022

E-commerce online store for branded tech keyboards and keycaps.

Full- Stack MEN web application that features 7 RESTful routes with full CRUD capabilities.

- JavaScript, CSS, HTML, Express.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Mongoose, Postman.
- Collaborated in a team of 3 software engineers in a 1-week sprint.
- Used Mongoose to define schemas for MongoDB collections for database.
- Implemented EJS template literal along with CSS3 and Bootstrap to provide enhanced UI.
- Utilized Git control during the production with frequent commits until deployment.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NS Global Commerce LLC

Founder | New York, NY 08/2017 - 12/2021

- ► Implemented new consumer service management tools, decreasing order-handling time by 50%.
- Managed website overhaul and rebranding, including the addition of e-commerce.
- Grew digital outreach with a 20% increase in revenue.
- Managed partnerships with manufacturers and suppliers.

Sishodia Law, P.C

Paralegal | New York, NY 01/2016 - 08/2017

- Coordinated Real Estate Law Firm operations to serve 100 + clients, including maintaining detail-oriented database records to ensure timely and appropriate care given to all clients
- · Handled quick-book entry for accurate accounting
- Achieved in-demand status amongst paralegal colleagues; often personally requested by senior partners to manage complex, deadline-intensive matter.

Sunny Way LLC

Co - Founder | Florida 01/2015 - Present

- Direct all activities related to dispatching, routing and tracking transportation vehicles.
- · Manage company finance, including budgeting and payroll, to fulfill fiscal strategic goals.
- Oversee productivity and routing software systems.
- Manage and promote the maintenance of working environment, including driving health and safety standards across an operational area.
- Lead strategic goal setting and analytical thinking.

VIEW PORTFOLIO



EDUCATION

General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive

Full-stack software development - intensive twelve-week, 420+ in-class hour program focused on product development fundamentals, object-oriented programming, MVC framework, data modeling, and team collaboration and communication strategies. Demonstrated technical proficiency through development of increasingly more advanced web applications.

Ivane Javakhishvili State University

Tbilisi, Georgia

Bachelor of Science: Science in Chemistry & Biology.